Video Editing
Schnitt
Galaxy 9000
Galaxy 9000
Wealth, fame, power...
Reichtum, Macht und Ruhm.
Timing
Timing
Drasleek PhosCity
Drasleek PhosCity
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates, obtained everything the world has to offer.
Der Mann, der sich dies alles erkämpft hatte,
Quality Control
Qualitätskontrolle
Galaxy 9000 Pepperjack
Galaxy 9000 Pepperjack vô danh Puma Floa arch1t3cht
Soundtracking
Vertonung
Halee
Halee
What he said in his final moments drove countless souls to the seas.
Als er hingerichtet wurde, waren seine letzten Worte:
Graphics
Grafiken
Datenshi
Datenshi
Karaoke
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
KaitouYahiko
You want my treasure? Go ahead.
„Ihr wollt meinen Schatz? Den könnt ihr haben! Sucht ihn doch!
Subtitle Editing
Untertitel Editing
Ravenfire Realfolk Zenef
akamizu
Find it!
Übersetzung
Translation
Crunchyroll akamizu
Everything is right where I left it!
Irgendwo hab ich den größten Schatz der Welt versteckt!“
Raws
Raws
df68
df68
People set their sights on the Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams.
Dieser Schatz ist das One Piece und er liegt irgendwo auf der Grand Line.
The world has truly entered the Great Pirate Era!
Damit brach das große Piratenzeitalter an!
We'
Wir
A
A
re go
fol
ri
ri
ing
gen
tta
tta
to
al
ke
ke
ga
le
no
no
th
un
yu
yu
er
se
me
me
up
ren
wo
wo
all
Träu
A
A
our
men.
ka
ka
dr
ki
ki
ri
ri
a
ea
tsu
a
tta
ms
me
tsu
ke
tta
no
yu
yu
me
me
wo
wo
ka
ka
ki
ki
a
a
tsu
tsu
me
me
We'
Wir
re go
fol
ing
gen
to
al
ga
le
th
un
er
se
up
ren
all
und
our
Sa
dr
Träu
and
zie
Sa
ga
ea
men.
set
hen
ga
shi
ms
hi
out
mo
shi
naus,
in
no
mo
um
se
wo
no
auf
ar
sa
wo
Schatz
ch
ga
sa
su
of
shi
ga
che
so
ni
shi
Sa
me
zu
ni
yu
Sa
ge
th
ku
yu
hen:
ing
no
ku
sa
to
ga
no
shi
fi
mo
shi
no
mo
wo
no
sa
sa
ga
ga
shi
ni
ni
yu
yu
ku
ku
no
no
sa
sa
and
und
set
zie
out
hen
in
hi
se
naus,
ar
um
ch
auf
of
Schatz
so
su
me
che
th
zu
ing
ONE
to
ge
ONE
PIECE
fi
hen:
PIECE
ONE
ONE
PIECE
Co
Ein
Ra
Ra
mp
Kom
shin
shin
as
pass
ba
ba
ses
hält
n
n
on
im
nan
nan
ly
Grun
te
te
ca
de
use
nur
juu
juu
del
auf.
tai
tai
ays
no
no
Ra
Ra
mo
mo
to
to
shin
shin
ba
ba
n
n
nan
nan
te
juu
juu
tai
tai
no
no
mo
mo
Co
Ein
mp
to
to
Kom
as
pass
ses
hält
on
im
ly
Grun
ca
de
use
nur
del
auf.
De
Mit
Ne
Ne
li
ho
tsu
tsu
ri
hem
ni
ni
ous
Fie
u
u
wi
ber
ka
ka
th
stell
sa
sa
fe
ich
re
re
ve
mich
r,
ans
ka
ka
I
Ruder.
Ne
Ne
ji
ji
ta
wo
wo
to
ke
ru
to
no
the
tsu
ru
sa
he
ni
no
u
tsu
ka
u
sa
sa
re
ka
ka
ji
ji
wo
wo
to
to
ru
ru
no
no
De
sa
sa
Mit
li
ho
ri
hem
ous
Fie
wi
ber
th
stell
fe
ich
ve
mich
r,
ans
I
Ruder.
If
Die
HO
HO
the
alte
KO
KO
du
Schatz
RI
RI
sty
kar
ka
ka
tr
te
bu
bu
ea
führt
tte
tte
su
zum
ta
ta
re
Ziel.
map
HO
ta
ka
HO
ra
has
no
ka
chi
be
zu
ra
KO
en
mo
no
RI
ve
ka
ri
bu
bu
tte
tte
ta
ka
ka
ra
ra
no
no
chi
chi
zu
zu
mo
mo
If
Die
the
alte
du
Wenn
sty
Ta
tr
Schatz
ea
Du
su
shi
re
kar
map
dir
has
ka
th
te
Ta
si
be
me
en
führt
shi
cher
it's
ta
ka
zum
ve
bist,
not
no
me
Ziel.
ri
ist
a
na
ta
es
fi
ra
le
kei
no
den
ed,
ne
ge
se
na
Le
nd!
tsu
ra
gen
den
ja
se
Ta
tsu
de!
ja
na
Ta
i!
na
shi
i!
ka
ka
me
me
ta
ta
no
no
na
ra
ra
den
den
se
se
tsu
tsu
ja
ja
na
na
i!
Wenn
th
Du
en
dir
it's
si
not
i!
a
cher
le
bist,
ge
ist
nd!
es
Wh
Und
Ko
Ko
en
ge
ji
ji
it
rät
n
n
co
man
te
te
mes
selbst
ki
ki
to
in
na
na
pe
ei
a
a
rs
nen
ra
ra
on
Sturm,
shi
shi
al
wa
wa
Ko
Ko
da
st
re
da
ka
or
no
re
ji
ji
n
te
te
ki
ki
na
na
a
a
ra
ra
shi
shi
wa
wa
da
da
re
re
ka
ka
Wh
no
en
Und
it
ge
co
rät
no
man
mes
selbst
to
in
pe
ei
rs
nen
on
Sturm,
al
kann
st
BA
or
man
ms,
I
si
sich
BA
O
mp
je
I
RI
ly
man
O
ZU
ri
des
RI
MU
de
Strö
ZU
no
ab
mung
MU
kka
oa
an
no
t
rd
BA
kka
ver
so
te
t
trau
BA
en.
me
I
's
O
RI
RI
ZU
ZU
MU
MU
no
no
kka
kka
t
t
te
te
si
kann
mp
man
ly
sich
ri
je
de
man
ab
des
oa
Strö
rd
mung
so
an
me
ver
one
Und
el
O
se
trau
's
so
bi
mo
or
en.
and
tun,
O
i
hy
als
pr
su
mo
wä
thm
go
et
re
i
se
end
nichts
su
ba
it
ge
go
ii!
is
we
se
O
n't
sen!
ba
mo
th
i
ii!
su
i
go
su
se
go
ba
se
ii!
ba
Und
ii!
so
and
tun,
pr
als
et
wä
end
re
it
nichts
is
ge
n't
we
th
sen!
We
Wir
A
A
're
fol
ri
ri
go
gen
tta
tta
ing
al
ke
ke
to
le
no
no
ga
un
yu
yu
th
se
me
me
er
ren
wo
wo
up
Träu
A
A
all
men.
ka
ka
our
ki
ki
ri
ri
a
dr
tta
a
tsu
ea
me
tta
ke
tsu
no
yu
yu
me
me
wo
wo
ka
ka
ki
ki
a
a
tsu
tsu
me
me
We
Wir
're
fol
go
gen
ing
al
to
le
ga
un
th
se
er
und
up
Sa
all
ren
our
zie
and
ga
Sa
Träu
dr
hen
set
shi
ga
men.
ea
hi
out
mo
shi
naus,
ms
no
in
um
mo
wo
se
auf
no
sa
ar
Schatz
wo
ga
ch
su
sa
shi
of
Sa
ga
che
so
ni
shi
zu
Sa
yu
me
ge
ni
ku
th
hen:
yu
no
ing
ga
ku
sa
to
shi
no
mo
shi
no
mo
wo
no
sa
sa
ga
ga
shi
ni
ni
yu
yu
ku
ku
no
no
sa
sa
and
und
set
zie
out
hen
in
hi
se
naus,
ar
um
ch
auf
of
Schatz
so
su
me
che
th
zu
ing
ge
to
hen:
fi
Willst
nd
PO
A
du
PO
KE
co
die
KE
TTO
in
Mün
TTO
no
no
ze
my
KO
KO
aus
po
IN
IN
mei
ck
ner
et,
Ta
PO
PO
KE
sche
TTO
KE
no
no
KO
KO
IN
IN
A
Willst
and
du
So
die
co
o
do
So
re
Mün
in
der
you
re
to
ze
in
lie
wa
to
You
aus
my
ber
nna
You
wan
mei
po
mein
be
wan
na
ner
ck
Freund
my
na
be
Ta
et,
sein?
fr
be
my
sche
ie
my
Friend?
Friend?
nd?
So
So
re
re
to
to
You
You
wan
wan
na
na
be
be
my
my
Friend?
and
o
do
der
you
lie
wa
ber
nna
mein
be
Freund
my
sein?
fr
We
ie
are,
nd?
are
We
on
are,
the
are
cruise!
on
We
are,
are,
are
are
on
on
the
the
cruise!
cruise!
We
We
are!
are!
Those three think they can mock me! Screw that!
Diese drei denken, sie könnten mich an der Nase rumführen. Nicht mit mir!
{Looks like I can consider this a declaration of war against me! - OG}{I'm going to consider this a formal declaration of war. - Z}I'm considering this a formal declaration of war.
Das kann ich dann wohl als eine Kriegserklärung auffassen.
Perfect timing, Mohji!
Da bist du ja, Mohji.
"Beast Tamer" Mohji First Mate, Buggy Pirates
Mohji der Dompteur Vizekapitän, Buggys Piratenbande
Would you mind
Würde es Ihnen etwas ausmachen,
if I took Roronoa Zoro's head?
wenn ich mir Roronoa Zoros Kopf hole?
Be my guest!
Nur zu.
Treasure
Schatz
What's with that dog?
Was ist mit dem Hund?
A dog!
Ah, ein Hund!
Hey, Zoro! It's not moving at all!
Ey, Zoro! Der bewegt sich keinen Millimeter!
Hell if I care! It can do whatever it wants!
Als ob mich das juckt! Der kann tun und lassen, was er will.
Think it's dead?
Ob der wohl tot ist?
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Ah! Aua, aua, aua!
{Ow! What're you doing, stupid dog?! - OG}Ow! What's the big deal, you stupid dog?!
Aua! Was tust du denn da, du blöder Kläffer?!
{Do you know the situation we're in right now?! - OG}{Would ya stop messin' around at a time like this?! - Z}Would you stop messing around at a time like this?!
Weißt du überhaupt, in was für einer Situation wir gerade stecken?!
Damn dog!
Verdammter Hund!
Not enough blood...
Ich hab zu viel Blut verloren...
Hey, Navigator!
Yo, Navigatorin!
I guess you can have this since you did save me!
Den kannst du wohl haben. Hast mich ja immerhin gerettet.
Oh! The key to the cage!
Oh! Der Schlüssel für den Käfig!
You went and got it for me?!
Den hast du für mich besorgt?
Now we're even.
Ich wollte dir bloß nichts schuldig bleiben.
I'm saved!
Ich bin gerettet!
Stupid dog! Stupid dog!
Du dumme Töle!
{That's not food! Gimme that key back! - OG}That's not food! Gimme back that key!
Das ist kein Fressen! Spuck den Schlüssel wieder aus!
Gimme! Gimme! Gimme!
Gib ihn mir schon zurück!
Stop that!
Aufhören!
{Quit bullying Chouchou, you young'uns! - OG}Quit bullying Chouchou, you delinquents!
Hört sofort auf, Shushu zu schikanieren, ihr Bengel!
Chouchou?
Shushu?
Who are you, old-timer?
Wer bist du, alter Mann?
I'm this town's mayor!
Ich bin der Bürgermeister dieser Stadt!
Boodle Harbor Village Mayor
Buddle Bürgermeister der Hafenstadt
Who are you?!
Wer seid ihr?
Huh?
Nanu?
How's Zoro?!
Wie geht’s Zoro?
He needs to see a doctor,
Er muss das von einem Arzt ansehen lassen,
but he said he'd sleep it off and went to bed.
aber er sagte, dass er es ausschlafen würde und ging zu Bett.
So this dog's name is Chouchou?
Dieser Hund heißt also Shushu?
What's he just sitting here for?
Wieso sitzt der hier nur so rum?
He's guarding the shop.
Er bewacht den Laden.
Oh! This is a... pet food shop?
Oh! Das ist ein Tierfutterladen.
{Yes. This shop's owner is a good friend of mine... - OG}Yes. A good friend of mine owned this shop.{Zenef: the present tense bugged me, but I didn't want to reveal just yet that the owner had died, so this is the compromise.}
Das siehst du richtig. Dieser Laden gehört einem guten Freund von mir.
There you go.
Bitte sehr.
{So I'm here to feed his dog in his place. - OG}I'm just here to feed his dog in his place.
Ich komme her, um seinen Hund an seiner Stelle zu füttern.
"In his place"?
An seiner Stelle?
Yes.
Ja.
{He died three months ago, from an illness. - OG}He got sick and passed away, oh, three months ago.
Er ist vor drei Monaten an den Folgen einer Krankheit verstorben.
{Don't tell me he's been waiting for his master to return all this time? - OG}You mean to tell us he's been waiting here for his master all this time?
Wartet er etwa schon die ganze Zeit auf die Rückkehr seines Herrchens?
That's the general consensus...
Das erzählt man sich,
but I don't think that's the case.
aber ich glaube nicht, dass das zutrifft.
Chouchou is a smart dog.
Shushu ist ein kluger Hund.
{He's probably long known that his master is dead. - OG}He's probably long since realized that his master passed on.
Ihm ist womöglich schon lange klar, dass sein Besitzer verstorben ist.
Then why is he guarding the shop?
Warum bewacht er dann den Laden?
{I think it's because this shop is a treasure in Chouchou's eyes. - OG}I believe it's because Chouchou regards this shop as his treasure.
Ich vermute, dass Shushu den Laden als einen Schatz betrachtet.
I think he continues to protects it in memory of his loving master.
Er bewacht ihn weiterhin,
{I've tried to make him evacuate on many occasions, - OG}I've tried to get him somewhere safer on many occasions,
Ich habe schon oft versucht, ihn fortzubringen,
but he won't take as much as a step away from here.
aber er entfernt sich keinen einzigen Schritt von hier.
Huh? What are those roars?!
Was ist das für ein Kampfschrei?!
It's him! Beast Tamer Mohji!
Er ist es! Mohji, der Dompteur!
What do you mean by "Beast Tamer"?!
Was meinen Sie mit „Dompteur“?
W-Wait! Hold on!
M-Moment mal! Warten Sie!
C'mon, something's on its way.
Jetzt komm schon, da kommt jemand!
Gimme back the key.
Rück den Schlüssel raus.
Oh, I see your friends have deserted you.
Oh, wie ich sehe, haben dich deine Freunde im Stich gelassen.
{Just after you managed to escape, too... - OG}And you only just escaped...
Dabei konntest du doch gerade erst flüchten.
Who are you?
Wer bist’n du?
I am Beast Tamer Mohji, a member of the Buggy Pirates.
Ich bin Mohji, der Dompteur, ein Mitglied von Buggys Piratenbande.
That sure is a weird animal suit you got on!
Echt ein eigenartiges Tierkostüm, was du da anhast.
How rude! This is my hair!
Wie unverschämt! Das sind meine Haare!
That's even weirder!
Ist ja noch eigenartiger.
Do you think you can rest easy because you're inside that cage?
Lehnst du dich zurück, nur weil du in diesem Käfig bist?
You must not know my terrifying skill!
Kennst du meine Fürchterlichkeit nicht?!
There is no animal in this world that Beast Tamer Mohji can't tame!
Auf dieser Welt gibt es kein Tier,
Shake!
Gib Pfote!
{You're nothing but a nameless sneak thief. - OG}You're just some nameless thief.
Du bist nichts als ein namenloser Gelegenheitsdieb.
{I have no interest in taking your life. Tell me where Roronoa Zoro is! - OG}I couldn't care less if you live or die. Tell me where Roronoa Zoro is!
Ich hab kein Interesse daran, dich zu töten.
No!
Will nicht!
Sic him, Richie!
Auf ihn, Richie!
Alright! The cage is open!
Jawoll! Der Käfig ist offen!
An instant death.
Ein sofortiger Tod.
Good boy, Richie.
Braver Richie.
{Now let's find Zoro so I can defeat him and increase my name! - OG}{Now let's find Zoro, defeat him, and bolster my reputation. - Z}Now let's find Zoro and defeat him to bolster my reputation.
Und jetzt spüre Zoro auf,
What is it?
Hm... Was ist?
Ah, a pet food store.
Ach, ein Tierfutterladen.
Fine, make your meal quick!
Na gut, aber iss schnell!
What the...?
Nanu?
{Don't tell me this is this pathetic little shop's guard dog? - OG}Is this mutt really trying to keep us out of this pathetic little shop?
Soll das etwa der Wachhund dieses mickrigen Tierfutterladens sein?
Phew, what a shock!
Puh, Schreck lass nach!
But at least I'm out of the cage.
Aber jetzt bin ich aus dem Käfig raus!
Alright!
Na gut! Jetzt ist es an der Zeit, sie alle zu vermöbeln,
How did you survive that?!
Wie bist du noch am Leben?!
You're alive!
Du lebst!
Is it wrong to be alive?
Stimmt was nicht damit?
{Being just fine after flying through houses isn't normal! - OG}People don't normally crash through buildings and walk away from it!
Es ist nicht normal, durch mehrere Häuser zu fliegen,
They don't?
Ist es nicht?
{What is your purpose for coming to this town? - OG}Why did you come to this town in the first place?
Welche Absichten haben dich in diese Stadt geführt?
{Why are you involved with those pirates? - OG}{Why are you mixed up with those pirates? - Z}Why get mixed up with those pirates?
Und was hast du mit denen zu schaffen?
I've just now decided on our goal.
Das hab ich gerade entschieden!
{To get a Grand Line map and a navigator! - OG}To get a map to the Grand Line and find a navigator!
Wir besorgen uns eine Karte der Grand Line und eine Navigatorin!
{I think that guy in the animal suit said he was looking for Zoro! - OG}That guy in the animal costume said he was looking for Zoro!
Dieser Typ im Tierkostüm hat doch gesagt, dass er nach Zoro sucht!
I gotta find him!
Ich seh mal nach ihm!
Chouchou. This shop belongs to the two of us!
Shushu. Dieser Laden gehört uns beiden!
This bag is too big for you, Chouchou!
Der Sack ist zu groß für dich, Shushu!
You don't want to get hurt, Chouchou!
Du willst dich doch nicht verletzen, Shushu!
Just leave it to me!
Überlass das nur mir!
Bad Chouchou! I told you not to eat the merchandise!
Böser Shushu! Ich hab dir doch verboten, die Ware zu essen!
Now let's chow down!
Hier, lass es dir schmecken!
Oh? So you want to fight...
Oh? Du stellst dich uns ja immer noch entgegen.
{Chouchou. I'm getting up in age now. - OG}Chouchou, I'm getting up there in years now.
Shushu. Ich habe jetzt ein gewisses Alter erreicht.
I gotta check in to the hospital.
Daher muss ich mal im Krankenhaus vorbeischauen.
But... I'll surely get better!
Aber mir wird es wieder besser gehen!
Guard the shop well until I come back!
Pass gut auf den Laden auf, bis ich zurückkomme!
Hold down the fort!
Halte hier die Stellung!
That tickles, Chouchou!
Das kitzelt, Shushu!
{I think it's because this shop is a treasure in Chouchou's eyes. - OG}I believe it's because Chouchou regards this shop as his treasure.
Ich vermute, dass Shushu den Laden als einen Schatz betrachtet.
I think he continues to protect it in memory of his loving master.
Er bewacht ihn weiterhin,
Damn it! That dog even bit me!
Scheiße! Dieser Köter hat mich sogar gebissen.
Wait! I just killed you!
Moment mal! Dich hab ich doch gerade umgebracht.
It'll take more than that to kill me!
So einfach beiß ich nicht ins Gras.
Crush his head for sure this time!
Dieses Mal musst du seinen Kopf auf jeden Fall zertrümmern!
I won't lose to some lion!
Ich werde doch nicht gegen irgendeinen Löwen verlieren!
Gum-Gum...
Gum-Gum...
Hammer!
Hammer!
Richie!
Richie!
Just what the hell are you?!
Was bist du?!
I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit!
Ich hab die Gum-Gum-Frucht gegessen.
{You mean you have Devil Fruit powers, - OG}You mean... just like Captain Buggy...
Soll das etwa heißen, dass du genau wie Kapitän Buggy
you have devil fruit powers?!
die Kräfte einer Teufelsfrucht hast?!
{A-all right! I peacefully apologize to you! - OG}I-I get the picture! Please accept my humble apology!
I-In Ordnung! Ich entschuldige mich ganz friedlich bei dir.
{You don't need to apologize now. - OG}It's too late for apologies
Du brauchst dich nicht mehr zu entschuldigen.
{'Cause that dog's treasure is never coming back. - OG}'cause that dog's treasure is gone forever.
Der Schatz dieses Hundes kommt nie wieder zurück.
{That's why I'm gonna kick your ass! - OG}And that's why... it's lights out for you!
Deshalb werde ich dich jetzt zu Brei schlagen!
Pirates are all the same, every last one!
Diese Piraten sind doch alle gleich, jeder einzelne von ihnen!
They take what people hold dear without a second thought!
Sie machen sich nichts aus dem, was anderen viel bedeutet.
So you survived, pirate!
Du bist also am Leben, Pirat!
{I figured the lion ate you for sure! - OG}{Figured the lion would for sure gobble you up! - Z}I figured the lion would've eaten you for sure!
Ich hätte schwören können, dieser Löwe hätte dich verspeist.
As a pirate, you'll end up doing the same thing!
Als Pirat würdest du doch dasselbe tun!
{You'll gather a crew and invade towns, - Z}{Once you gather your crew, you'll invade towns,}You'll gather a crew and raid town after town!
Ich sollte dich besser direkt umbringen,
I should just kill you right here instead!
bevor du eine Crew versammeln und genauso Leute angreifen kannst!
Hey! Stop it, young lady!
Ganz ruhig. Hör auf damit, Mädchen!
As if you could ever kill me.
Als ob du mich jemals töten könntest.
Let's test that theory!
Das werden wir doch mal sehen!
I said stop! What's with you people?!
Aufhören, hab ich gesagt! Was stimmt nicht mit euch?!
This is all I was able to rescue.
Das ist alles, was ich zurückholen konnte.
That bastard went and ate the rest!
Dieses Vieh hat den Rest verschlungen.
{He... fought with that lion. For that dog's sake... - OG}He... fought with that lion. All for that dog's sake.
Er... hat für den Hund gegen diesen Löwen gekämpft.
You fought good!
Du hast gut gekämpft!
{I didn't see your fight, but I can tell! - OG}I didn't see you in action, but I can tell!
Hab’s zwar nicht gesehen, aber ich weiß es einfach.
Yeah! Good luck to you, too!
Ja! Ich wünsche dir auch viel Glück!
You were beaten?!
Du wurdest besiegt?!
I-I'm very sorry, Captain Buggy!
E-Es tut mir unendlich leid, Käpt’n Buggy.
Mohji! I can't believe you'd lose to Zoro!
Mohji! Ich kann nicht fassen, dass du gegen Zoro verlieren konntest!
{No, it wasn't Zoro! It was that Straw Hat! - OG}No, it wasn't Zoro! It was Straw Hat!
Nein, es war nicht Zoro, sondern dieser Strohhut!
What?! You got beat by the kid in the straw hat?!
Wie bitte?! Diese Rotznase mit dem Strohhut hat dich besiegt?!
He ate the... Gum...
Er hat die Gu...
Now I'm pissed!
Jetzt hab ich die Schnauze voll!
{Prepare all the Special Buggy Balls we have! - OG}Ready all the Special Buggy Balls!
Bereitet sämtliche Spezial- Buggy-Kugeln vor, die wir haben!
I'm gonna blow this entire town to smithereens!
Ich werde die gesamte Stadt in Schutt und Asche legen!
Sorry for earlier!
Das von vorhin tut mir leid.
Huh?
Was?
I didn't mean to yell at you...
Ich wollte dich nicht anschreien.
It's okay! You've been through a lot!
Schon gut! Du hast eine Menge durchgemacht.
{I don't feel like hearing about it though. - OG}I don't need the details, though.
Hab aber eigentlich keine Lust, mir das alles anzuhören.
I'm so pathetic!
Ich bin so armselig!
{Chouchou and this young'un will fight so hard, - OG}If Chouchou and this youngster won't back down,
Shushu und dieser Jungspund führen so harte Kämpfe,
{yet why must I, the mayor, sit by and watch our town be obliterated?! - OG}then why am I, as mayor, content to watch the town get trashed?!
aber ich als Bürgermeister sitze untätig herum
Calm down, Mayor!
Beruhigen Sie sich!
{Forty years ago, this place was nothing but barren land. - OG}Forty years ago, this place was nothing but wilderness.
Vor 40 Jahren befand sich an diesem Ort nichts als Ödland.
We all worked together to clear the land, make fields,
Mit vereinten Kräften haben wir das Gebiet gerodet, Felder angelegt,
open stores, and build our town.
Läden eröffnet und unsere Stadt aufgebaut.
{This town is a treasure to me and all the citizens! - OG}This town is a treasure to me and all its citizens!
Diese Stadt ist ein Schatz für mich und all ihre Bewohner!
{I cannot let them domineer over it any more! - OG}I won't let them have their way with it any longer!
Ich kann ihre Unterdrückung nicht länger dulden!
Fire a Special Buggy Ball! Blow the town away!
Feuert eine Spezial-Buggy-Kugel. Sprengt die Stadt weg!
Even my own house...
Sogar mein eigenes Haus...
Zoro's sleeping in there!
Zoro schläft doch da drin!
That young man must be dead...
Er weilt nicht mehr unter uns...
Hey! Zoro! Are you alive?!
Hey! Zoro! Bist du am Leben?!
{That's one hell of a way to wake a guy up. - OG}That's a hell of a way to wake a guy up.
Das ist vielleicht ’ne Art, jemanden aufzuwecken...
Not enough sleep...
Ich konnte nicht mal ausschlafen...
And just how did you survive?!
Wie bist du da lebend rausgekommen?
Thank goodness! You're alive!
Gott sei Dank! Du lebst!
{I refuse to let them get away with this! - OG}No more sitting idly by while they run wild here!
Damit werde ich sie nicht davonkommen lassen.
I've had it up to here!
Ich kann das nicht länger ertragen.
{Some random scum has no right to suddenly destroy our 40 years! - OG}These scumbags have zero right to trample on these forty years!
Solch ein dahergelaufener Abschaum hat kein Recht,
I am this town's mayor!
Ich bin der Bürgermeister dieser Stadt!
I will protect this town!
Ich werde sie beschützen!
Stop! Stop, Mayor!
Tun Sie nichts Unüberlegtes!
{There are fights a man cannot run from! - OG}There are fights a man can't run away from!
Es gibt Kämpfe, vor denen ein Mann nicht flüchten kann!
Isn't that right, kiddo?!
Stimmt doch, oder, Kind?
Right, old guy!
Das stimmt, alter Mann!
Don't egg him on!
Stachel ihn nicht auch noch an!
{What can he possibly do by going to see them?! It's reckless! - OG}What's he gonna change by facing them?! It's reckless!
Was soll er denn ausrichten, wenn er zu ihnen geht? Das ist leichtsinnig!
It's absolutely reckless!
Das ist mir völlig bewusst!
I'm coming for you, Buggy the Clown!
Warte nur, Buggy, der Clown!
The mayor was crying...
Der Bürgermeister hat geweint...
He was? Not that I could see.
Hat er? Hab ich nicht gesehen.
Looks like the party's getting more exciting!
Jetzt scheint die Party richtig loszugehen!
You said it!
In der Tat!
This is no time to be laughing!
Da gibt es nichts zu lachen!
It's okay! I like that old guy!
Alles gut! Ich mag diesen alten Knacker.
I'd never let him die!
Den lass ich nicht sterben!
In that case...
Wenn das so ist...
{You're gonna go too?! With that wound?! - OG}You're going too?! But you're wounded!
Du gehst auch? Mit dieser Wunde?!
{The injury to my name is much worse than the injury to my gut! - OG}Getting thrashed hurts my rep way more than the gut wound itself.
Im Gegensatz zum Schaden an meinem Namen
We're headed for the Grand Line.
Unser Ziel ist die Grand Line.
{So we're gonna steal that map back now! - OG}So we're gonna swipe that map back from them!
Also werden wir uns diese Karte jetzt zurückstehlen!
Join our crew, Nami!
Schließ dich unserer Bande an, Nami! Na los!
I won't become a pirate.
Ich werde niemals ein Pirat sein.
{How about we team up for our common goal? - OG}How about this? We team up to achieve a common goal!
Warum arbeiten wir nicht für unser gemeinsames Ziel zusammen?
The second shot is ready, sir!
Die zweite Kugel ist bereit, Sir!
Alright! Fire!
Sehr schön! Abfeuern!
Get out here, Buggy the Clown!
Komm raus, Buggy der Clown!
I am Mayor Boodle!
Ich bin Bürgermeister Buddel!
{This town is our treasure! I've come to protect it! Fight me! - OG}This town is our treasure, so I'm going to protect it by taking you out!
Diese Stadt ist unser Schatz! Ich bin hier, um sie zu beschützen!
What are you, stupid?! Treasure is gold, silver, and jewels!
Bist du komplett dämlich? Gold, Silber und Juwelen sind Schätze!
This town, a treasure?! Cut the crap!
Diese Stadt soll ein Schatz sein? Dass ich nicht lache!
You'd never understand how I feel
Du würdest nie verstehen, wie ich mich fühle...
{I'm soon going to conquer the Grand Line and flashily obtain all of the world's riches! - OG}Soon, I'll conquer the Grand Line and flashily obtain all of the world's riches!
Ich bin der Mann, der die Grand Line erobern
The world's riches are mine!
Die Schätze dieser Welt gehören mir!
No one else in this world needs treasure but me!
Außer mir braucht in dieser Welt niemand Schätze!
{If this town's that important to you, shall I destroy you with it?! - OG}Since you love this town so much, shall I level it along with you?
Wenn dir diese Stadt so wichtig ist,
Quit blowing hot air and fight me!
Hör auf zu brabbeln und kämpf gegen mich!
Don't get cocky now!
Werd jetzt nicht übermütig.
I won't let you destroy this town even if it costs me my life!
Ich werde dich diese Stadt nicht zerstören lassen!
Fire!
Schießt!
The straw hat guy!
Der Strohhutbengel!
I'm here to kick your ass, just like I promised!{Z - important to keep this line as is, since this is the wording Luffy uses toward Buggy in the previous episode.}
Ich bin hier, um dir wie versprochen den Hintern zu versohlen!
Straw Hat?!
Der Strohhut?!
{How dare you just come waltzing back here... - OG}How dare you just waltz back here...
Was fällt dir ein, wieder hier bei Kapitän Buggy aufzukreuzen?!
Listen! All I want is the map and the treasure!
Pass mal auf!
Yeah, we know.
Ja, schon klar.
Youngsters... Why'd you come here?!
Kinder... Warum seid ihr hier?
{Stay out of this, you're outsiders! - OG}This isn't your business, so butt out!
Haltet euch da raus. Das ist nicht eure Angelegenheit.
This is my fight! I will protect my town!
Das ist mein Kampf. Ich werde diese Stadt beschützen!
Now stop meddling!
Mischt euch nicht ein!
What the hell?!
Was zur Hölle sollte das denn?!
Why did you attack the mayor?!
Warum hast du den Bürgermeister angegriffen?!
He was in the way!
War im Weg!
Good thinking.
Gut mitgedacht.
{No doubt this old man plans to die otherwise. - OG}No doubt this geezer was prepared to die.
Der Greis hatte zweifellos vor, sein Leben zu opfern.
This is for the best.
So ist es am besten.
But this is going overboard!
Du hast doch eine an der Klatsche!
There were plenty of other ways you could've done it!
Dafür hätte es auch noch genügend andere Lösungen gegeben!
Hey, Big Nose!
Hey du! Riesennase!
That's the one thing you shouldn't say!
Genau das solltest du nicht sagen!
You're dead meat, you flashy mongrel!
Verdammt seist du, störrischer Strohbursche!
How dare you...
Wie kannst du es wagen...?
Flashily fire the Buggy Ball!
Feuert die Buggy-Kugel!
Why'd you say that, you idiot!
Warum hast du das gesagt, du Schwachmat?!
Hey, Luffy! Run!
Hey, Luffy! Lauf!
That...
So was...
Time to blow up!
Ich spreng dich in Fetzen!
...won't work on me!
wird bei mir nicht klappen!
Gum-Gum...
Gum-Gum...
Balloon!
Ballon!
What is that guy?!
Was ist der Kerl?!
But the Buggy Ball will...
Die Buggy-Kugel kann doch unmöglich...
He bounced it back!
Er hat sie abprallen lassen!
Give us a heads up first, will ya?!
Klär einen doch mal vorher auf...
{Alright! Now there's fewer enemies! - OG}Alright! Fewer enemies now!
Volltreffer! Schon sind wir ’n paar los.
Really, what are you?!
Was um alles in der Welt bist du bitte?!
{You really know how to freak people out... - OG}You had me there for a sec.
Kannst einen echt wahnsinnig machen.
{I knew something was weird from the time you fought that lion! - OG}Ever since fighting that lion, I knew you weren't quite normal!
Schon seit deinem Kampf gegen den Löwen wusste ich,
No human can do that! Explain yourself!
Kein Mensch wäre dazu imstande!
What was that balloon-inflating thing you just did?!
Was hast du da gerade für ein Aufblasballon-Zeug abgezogen?!
That's Gum-Gum Balloon!
Das war der Gum-Gum-Ballon!
And how did you do that?!
Ich will wissen, was es damit auf sich hat!
What are you, a monster?!
Was bist du, ein Monster?!
How dare you flashily try to do me in...
Wie kannst du versuchen,
He used his henchmen as shields!
Er hat seine Schergen echt als Schutzschild missbraucht.
What happened here?!
Was ist hier geschehen?!
You!
Ah! Du bist’s!
Hey!
Tag!
The straw hat guy!
Der Strohhutjunge!
C-C-Captain Buggy! Be careful!
K-Käpt’n Buggy! Sehen Sie sich vor!
He has devil fruit powers too!
Er hat auch Teufelsfrucht-Kräfte!
He's a rubber person!
Der Junge ist ein Gummimensch!
What?!
Wie war das?
Rubber person?!
Gummimensch?
Yeah! See!
Jo! Schau mal!
A devil fruit...
Eine Teufelsfrucht also.
{That explains how he bounced a Buggy Ball back. - OG}That explains how he bounced back the Buggy Ball.
Das erklärt, wie er die Buggy-Kugel zurückschleudern konnte.
Cabaji "the Acrobat" (Second) First Mate, Buggy Pirates
Cabaji der Akrobat 2. Kommandant, Buggys Piratenbande
{This is the greatest insult we've had since we hoisted our flag... - OG}This is the greatest insult since we hoisted our flag.
Das ist die größte Beleidigung, seit wir unsere Flagge gehisst haben...
Captain.
Kapitän.
{Oh, Cabaji! I'm so angry I can't even fart. - OG}{Oh, Cabaji! I'm so angry I can't even speak. - arch/Realfolk}Oh, Cabaji! I'm so angry I'm seeing red.
Oh, Cabaji! Ich bin so wütend, dass ich nicht mal einen fahr’n lassen kann.
Cabaji! What the hell did you do to Richie?!
Cabaji! Was hast du Großkotz mit Richie angestellt?!
This cat?
Die Katze?
{I used him to shield me so I wouldn't get my clothes dirty. - Z}I used it to shield me so I wouldn't get my clothes dirty.
Ich hab sie als Schild benutzt, damit meine Kleidung nicht schmutzig wird.
Richie!
Richie!
Hey, Richie! Say something! Are you all right?!
Hey, Richie! Sag schon was! Geht es dir gut?
Richie!
Richie!
Dammit, you bastard!
Du verfluchter Akrobatenhampel!
Out of the way!
Aus dem Weg!
No, you get outta my way!
Geh du uns aus dem Weg!
Captain Buggy.
Kapitän Buggy.
Yes, Cabaji?
Was denn, Cabaji?
Please leave this to me.
Bitte überlassen Sie das mir.
Sounds good!
Gern! Zeig ihnen deine Akrobatenshow.
I, First Mate Cabaji the Acrobat,
Ich, Kommandant Cabaji, der Akrobat,
will manifest Captain Buggy's displeasure!
werde euch Kapitän Buggys Wut spüren lassen!
I'll clash swords with you.
Einen Schwertkampf kannst du gerne haben!
Quite the honor, Roronoa Zoro.
Es ist mir eine Ehre, Roronoa Zoro,
{To think I would get to slay you, as a swordsman myself. - OG}As a swordsman myself, I am happy to cut you down.
dass ich dich als Schwertkämpfer, wie ich selbst einer bin, töten darf.
Hey, Zoro! You should really rest! I'll handle this!
Ey, Zoro. Du solltest dich echt ausruhen. Ich regel das.
Stay out of this!
Halt dich da raus!
{That's the stab wound the captain gave him. The fool... - OG}That's the stab wound the captain gave him. What a fool.
Das ist doch die Stichwunde vom Käpt’n. Dieser Trottel...
Acrobatics: Dire Fire!
Akrobatentechnik: Feuerspucker!
Something wrong?
Was hast du denn?
I swear I didn't kick you that hard.
So hart hab ich dich doch gar nicht getreten.
He fights dirty, going after his injury like that!
Ein schmutziger Trick! Er hat es auf seine Wunde abgesehen!
Acrobatics: Steamy Hot Spring Murder Mystery!
Akrobatentechnik: Mord im Nebel!
Acrobatics, my ass!
Akrobatentechnik am Arsch!
{That's just an ordinary cloud of dust! - OG}That's just kicking up dust!
Ist doch bloß eine gewöhnliche Staubwolke!
He did it again!
Er hat es wieder getan!
{What's wrong? A grown man moaning is disgraceful! - OG}What's wrong? A grown man wailing is disgraceful!
Was ist denn? Echt erbärmlich, als gestandener Mann so rumzustöhnen.
Well? Now do you see how foolish it was
Nun? Erkennst du jetzt, wie töricht es von dir war,
to make an enemy of the Buggy Pirates?
dir die Buggy-Piraten zum Feind zu machen?
{He's hurt so bad it's almost mystifying that he's still alive! - OG}{As hurt as he is, it's just weird that he's even still alive! - Z}As hurt as he is, it's a miracle he's still alive!
Bei dieser Verletzung grenzt es an ein Wunder, dass er noch lebt!
Why are you just standing there watching?!
Was schaust du da eigentlich tatenlos zu?!
He's gonna get killed!
Man wird ihn noch umbringen!
Roronoa Zoro...
Roronoa Zoro...
accept defeat!
ist besiegt!
Annoying bastard!
Nervtötender Einradkasper!
Is poking my wound...
Macht es so viel Spaß,...
that much fun?!
in meiner Wunde rumzustochern?!
Ow!
Autsch!
Wh-Why didn't you dodge that?!
W-Wieso bist du nicht ausgewichen?
Is that enough of a handicap for you?
Reicht dir das als Handicap?
{Now I'll show you the difference in level between you and me! - OG}Now I'll show you... just how outclassed you are!
Ich zeig dir jetzt mal,
So cool!
So cool!
So this is Roronoa Zoro, huh?
Das ist also Roronoa Zoro, hm?
You think you can mock me...
Du willst mich verschaukeln.
{My swords aim to be the world's greatest! - OG}It's my dream to be the world's greatest swordsman.
Meine Schwerter werden einmal die besten dieser Welt sein!
{I can't lose even once to anyone who is considered a swordsman! - OG}I can't lose even once to anyone who's considered a swordsman!
Ich kann es mir kein einziges Mal leisten,
I see...
Verstehe...
A strong resolve keeps you going.
Diese starke Entschlossenheit treibt dich weiter an.
But never fear.
Aber hab keine Angst.
{Wounds as bad as yours will be more than enough of an excuse... - OG}Wounds as bad as yours will make an excellent excuse...
So schlimme Wunden wie die deinen genügen vollkommen...
to explain why you lost to me!
als Entschuldigung, gegen mich zu verlieren!
To hell with that...
Verarsch mich nicht.
If I lose to someone like you with such light injuries,
Wenn ich mit solchen Kratzern gegen jemanden wie dich verliere,
{I won't have much of a bright future ahead of me! - OG}then my future isn't looking too bright!
sieht meine Zukunft nicht vielversprechend aus!
Why, you...!
Du Mistkerl...
Do it, Zoro!
Los, Zoro!
This is too much for me.
Ich kann mir das nicht länger geben.
{You pirates can injure yourselves for all I care! - OG}You pirates go and injure yourselves all you want.
Ihr Piraten könnt euch gegenseitig aufschlitzen, so viel ihr wollt.
{It doesn't matter to me whether you guys win or lose! - OG}Besides, I have no stake in whether you win or lose.
Mich interessiert es nicht die Bohne, ob ihr gewinnt oder verliert.
{I'm gonna use this chance to swipe their treasure and get outta here! - OG}Now's a good chance for me to swipe the treasure and make tracks.
Ich schnapp mir bei dieser Gelegenheit ihre Schätze
Let's team up again if we ever get the chance!
Falls sich noch mal was ergibt, können wir ja zusammenarbeiten.
See ya! Good luck with the fight!
Man sieht sich! Gutes Gelingen bei eurem Kampf!
Yeah! Thanks!
Alles klar! Danke!
Taste my ultimate acrobatic move!
Eine Kostprobe meiner ultimativen Akrobatentechnik!
Acrobatics: 100 Whirling Kamikaze Dervishes!
Akrobatentechnik: 100 Kamikaze-Kreisel!
Acrobatics: Alpine Ascent!
Akrobatentechnik: Gipfelstürmer!
Acrobatics: Midsummer Fireworks!
Akrobatentechnik: Kühles Feuerwerk!
Whoa, he's soaring!
Woah, der fliegt echt hoch!
Unicycle Thorn!
Einrad-Stich!
Ground-hugging Part-Part Cannon!
Trenn-Trenn-Kanone: Anschleicher!
Cabaji! I'll hold Zoro down! Finish him off!
Cabaji! Mach ihn kalt! Ich halte diesen Zoro fest!
As you wish!
Wie Sie wünschen!
You bastards!
Ihr hinterhältigen Schweine!
Luffy!
Luffy!
Curse you!
S-Scheißkerl!
Zoro's fight...
Lass deine Finger aus Zoros Zweikampf.
I can defeat you easily enough without my captain's help!
Für mich ist es ein Leichtes, dich zu besiegen.
Enough... I'm tired...
Das reicht... Ich hab genug.
Finally given up, have you?
Jetzt gibst du also doch auf, was?
Though I must say, I'm impressed you could fight with such injuries.
Ich bin beeindruckt, dass du mit diesen Wunden kämpfen konntest.
I meant I'm tired... of your crappy-ass acrobatics!
Ich meinte damit, dass ich genug von deinen dämlichen Zirkustricks habe!
Then I'll finish you off... with my...
Dann versetze ich dir jetzt...
real swordsmanship!
mit meinen wahren Schwertkünsten den Gnadenstoß!
Die!
Stirb!
Oni...
Oni...
Giri!
Giri!
Cabaji!
Cabaji!
We, the Buggy Pirates...
Wir, die Buggy-Piraten,
beaten by pesky thieves!
besiegt von bloßen Gelegenheitsdieben...
"Thieves"? Nah...
Wir sind keine Gelegenheitsdiebe.
We're pirates!
Sondern Piraten!
Luffy! I'm gonna sleep now!
Luffy! Ich leg mich jetzt schlafen.
Right! I'll handle the rest!
Gut! Ich nehm den Rest in die Hand!
You guys are pirates?!
Ihr Luschen wollt Piraten sein?
Yeah! We're headed for the Grand Line!
Ja! Wir sind auf dem Weg zur Grand Line.
{That's no simple voyage nameless bums like you can handle, dimwit! - OG}Half-baked nobodies like you can't handle that kind of voyage, dimwit!
Das ist kein entspannter Ausflug, dem ihr Penner gewachsen wärt, Knalltüte.
What are you gonna do in the Grand Line, anyway?!
Was wollt ihr überhaupt auf der Grand Line machen?
Go on a sightseeing trip or something?
Soll das ein Sightseeing-Trip werden, oder was?
Become King of the Pirates!
Ich werde der König der Piraten.
Get real, you flashy fool!
Jetzt mal im Ernst, du verwirrte Vogelscheuche!
If you're King of the Pirates,
Du willst der König der Piraten werden?
does that make me God of the Pirates?!
Was bin ich dann, Gott?!
{I'm gonna be King of the Pirates and obtain this world's treasures! - OG}I'll be King of the Pirates and obtain the world's treasures!
Ich werde der König der Piraten sein und alle Schätze der Welt an mich reißen!
You're dreaming!
Hör auf zu träumen!
You're annoying.
Du bist echt lästig.
Just bring it on already!
Jetzt komm endlich her!
{Seeing that straw hat of yours brings back memories of him... - OG}That straw hat of yours reminds me of a certain man,
Dieser Strohhut auf deinem Kopf weckt Erinnerungen an ihn.
and it bugs me!
Das kotzt mich an!
{Memories of that damn cheeky red-haired man! - OG}It reminds me of that dog... of that red-haired bastard!
Erinnerungen an diesen schrecklich vorlauten, rothaarigen Mann!
"Red-haired"?!
Rothaarig?
{Red-haired... Does that mean you know Shanks?! - OG}You said "red-haired"! Does that mean you know Shanks?!
Rothaarig... Soll das etwa heißen, dass du Shanks kennst?
Huh? Yeah, but what's it to you?
Hm? Stimmt, aber wieso juckt’s dich?
Do you... know where he is?!
Wo ist er gerade?
Who can say?! I might know where he is,
Mal sehen... Vielleicht weiß ich es, vielleicht aber auch nicht.
{What're you talking about? Are you stupid or something? - OG}That makes no sense. Are you an idiot?
Was laberst du da? Biste bekloppt oder so?
Look who's talking!
Nicht annähernd so bekloppt wie du!
{I ain't nice enough of a guy to just tell you what you wanna know! - OG}I'm not nice enough of a guy to just tell you what you wanna know!
Ich bin kein Gutmensch, der dir einfach sagen würde, was du wissen willst!
Then I'll make you tell me!
Dann werde ich dich eben dazu zwingen!
I'll kill you before that ever happens!
Bevor es dazu kommen kann, bringe ich dich um!
I doubt rubber can bounce back blades...
Ich bezweifle, dass Gummi gegen Klingen immun ist.
Nope, it can't!
Jau, ist es nicht.
Part-Part Slicecracker!
Trenn-Trenn-Senbei!
Can't move in midair, can you?!
In der Luft kannste nicht ausweichen, was?
Can too!
Kann ich wohl!
Oh, my! Quite interesting!
Oh, ziemlich kreativ!
Same to you!
Du aber auch!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Your moves are creative,
Wirklich interessante Fähigkeiten.
but they leave you wide open!
Aber sie machen dich auch angreifbar.
Time to carve you up!
Ich werd dich zerstückeln!
Gum-Gum...
Gum-Gum:
Part-Part Quick Escape!
Trenn-Trenn-Notrettung!
Sickle!
Sichel!
Not good enough, "Gum-Gum"!
Netter Versuch, Gum-Gum!
{Damn, you keep breaking into pieces! - OG}Damn, you keep coming apart!
Verdammt, du trennst dich ständig in Einzelteile auf.
{Wh-What a fight. It's almost like I'm dreaming... - OG}Wh-What a fight. It's like something out of a dream.
W-Was für ein Kampf... Fast, als würde ich träumen.
H-Hey... You see that?
Hey! Hast du das gerade gesehen?
You dumbass! Keep pretending to be knocked out!
Trottel! Stell dich weiter bewusstlos!
Get caught up in that, and you'd never have enough lives to survive!
Wenn du da reingerätst, helfen dir all die Leben dieser Welt nichts!
Part-Part Cannon!
Trenn-Trenn-Kanone!
Separate!
Amputation!
Well?! Do you see now, short stuff?!
Wie sieht’s aus? Schnallst du es jetzt, Zwerg?
You bastard!
Du Mistkerl!
{Was I not supposed to scratch your face or something? - OG}Oh? Can't handle a little scratch to your face?
Was sagst du? Hätte ich dein Gesicht nicht ankratzen dürfen, oder so?
How dare you...
Wie kannst du es wagen...?
How dare you damage this hat!
Wie kannst du es wagen, seinen Hut zu beschädigen?!
Huh?
Bitte?
This is my treasure!
Das ist mein Schatz!
{Whoever damages this hat absolutely must pay! - OG}No one damages this hat and gets away with it!
Wer diesen Hut beschädigt, muss dafür büßen!
Yeah. I swore to the person who gave me this straw hat
Genau. Dem, der mir diesen Strohhut gegeben hat, hab ich geschworen,
that I'd gather a crew and become a pirate!
eine Crew zu versammeln und ein Pirat zu werden!
I thought there was nothing that could faze him...
Dabei dachte ich, dass ihn nichts aus der Fassung bringen könnte.
but he looks pretty upset.
Dass ihn so etwas so sehr aufbringen könnte...
It would seem that hat has a history to it.
Hinter dem Hut steckt wohl eine längere Geschichte.
That's right!
Richtig!
Is it that important of a hat?
Ist das so ein wichtiger Hut?
If so...
Wenn er so wichtig ist,
then protect it better!
dann gib besser darauf Acht!
I'll leave this hat with you.
Dann vertraue ich dir diesen Hut an.
It's dear to me.
Er ist mir sehr wichtig.
Take good care of it!
Gib also gut drauf Acht!
Come bring it back to me someday...
Bring ihn mir eines Tages zurück,
once you've become a great pirate!
wenn aus dir ein großer Pirat geworden ist!
That's our promise... Luffy!
So lautet unser Versprechen, Luffy!
You call this filthy straw hat a treasure?
Diesen versifften Strohhut nennst du einen Schatz?
Cut the crap!
Mach dich doch nicht lächerlich.
{That's the hat Shanks and I swore over! - OG}Shanks and I made a promise on that hat!
Mit diesem Hut haben Shanks und ich uns ein Versprechen gegeben!
What?!
Was?!
Meaning this is Shanks' hat?!
Dann ist das Shanks’ Hut?!
No wonder it seemed familiar!
Kein Wunder, dass er mir bekannt vorkam.
He always wore this around me!
Den hat er an meiner Seite immer getragen!
{You and Shanks sailed on the same ship?! - OG}You and Shanks sailed aboard the same ship?!
Du und Shanks seid auf demselben Schiff gereist?!
{Yeah, back when we were pirates-in-training. - OG}Oh, yeah, back during our pirate apprenticeships.
Richtig. Damals, als wir beide Piratenlehrlinge waren.
We were shipmates...
Wir waren Kameraden.
{That damn detestable, red-haired bastard! - OG}me and that damn, detestable, red-haired bastard!
Dieser dreckige, widerwärtige Rothaar-Bastard!
Shanks is a great man!
Shanks ist ein großartiger Mann!
You, his shipmate?!
Du sollst sein Kamerad gewesen sein?!
Don't compare yourself to him!
Setz dich nicht mit ihm gleich!
Part-Part Quick Escape!
Trenn-Trenn-Notrettung!
Hi, I'm Buggy!
Ich bin’s, Buggy!
{Never say you and Shanks are comrades ever again! - OG}Never say you and Shanks were shipmates ever again!
Nenn dich nie wieder einen Kameraden von Shanks!
I can say whatever I want about Shanks!
Ich kann über Shanks sagen, was immer ich will!
Tell me! What happened between you and Shanks?!
Raus damit! Was ist zwischen dir und Shanks vorgefallen?
{Damn it! How dare you tear up my treasure! - OG}Damn! You actually ripped up my treasure!
Scheißdreck! Wie kannst du meinen Schatz zerfetzen?!
Wanna know that badly?
Willst du es so unbedingt wissen?
He's the one person... I absolutely cannot forgive!
Ich kann ihm niemals verzeihen!
I'll curse him for the rest of my life!
Ich werde ihn für den Rest seines Daseins verfluchen!
I'll never forgive him!
Ihm werde ich niemals vergeben!